https://www.macromatic.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.macromatic.com.
Macromatic can be reached via email at sales@macromatic.com, by telephone at 800-238-7474 or by mail:
Macromatic Industrial Controls, Inc.
W134N5345 Campbell Drive
Menomonee Falls, WI 53051
Respecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important to Macromatic. Macromatic will not sell, rent or give away your email address or personal information at any time. Macromatic collects anonymous statistical data which is not personally identifiable. The information collected is used for marketing or sales purposes only.
If you do not want to receive emails, periodic mailings or telephone contact from Macromatic with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events, please send an email to the above address, call the above telephone number or write to the above address. Please provide your exact name and email address. Your name will be removed from the list within 72 hours.
This site contains links to other sites. Macromatic is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of linked websites. Macromatic encourages users to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy policy may be changed from time to time.
Revised Privacy Policies will be posted here. If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact Macromatic at sales@macromatic.com.
where to buy
support
resources
Recent News
Oct2020
Macromatic Names Christopher Curtis as Non-Executive Chairman
Jun2020
Triplex Pump Control Using Cost-saving Alternating Relays
May2020
Our 45th Anniversary: A Message to our Employees and Customers
Apr2020
Macromatic Recognized as Outstanding Supplier by Grainger
©2020 Macromatic Industrial Controls, Inc.W134N5345 Campbell Drive
Menomonee Falls, WI 53051
800-238-7474 • 262-781-3366
Rep Login | Newsletter Sign Up | Articles | Employment | Privacy Policy | Sitemap
Knowledgebase General | Alternating Relays | Current Sensing Relays | Intrinsically Safe Barrier Relays | Liquid Level Control Relays | Seal Leak Relays | Three-Phase Monitor Relays | Time Delay Relays | Voltage Monitor Relays
©2020 Macromatic Industrial Controls, Inc.W134N5345 Campbell Drive
Menomonee Falls, WI 53051
800-238-7474 • 262-781-3366
Rep Login | Newsletter Sign Up | Articles | Employment | Privacy Policy | Sitemap
Knowledgebase General | Alternating Relays | Current Sensing Relays | Intrinsically Safe Barrier Relays | Liquid Level Control Relays | Seal Leak Relays | Three-Phase Monitor Relays | Time Delay Relays | Voltage Monitor Relays
